const e="english",o=200,a=75,t=[{id:373,question:"He needn't have bought that new table ",option:{a:"It isn't possible that he bought the table ",b:"He bought the table, but it wasn't necessary ",c:"He didn’t buy the table because it wasn't necessary",d:"He doesn't need to buy the table "},section:"select the option that bost explains the information conveyed in the sentence.",image:"",answer:"b",solution:"",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2008",questionNub:null,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:374,question:"Thanks to that phone call, I was able to obtain the visa,",option:{a:"in spite of that phone call, I obtained the vist ",b:" It was because of that phone call that the visa",c:"I am grateful to whoever phoned me and I obtained the visa",d:"If I had not recieved that phone call, I would not have obtained the visa."},section:"select the option that bost explains the information conveyed in the sentence.",image:"",answer:"b",solution:"",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2008",questionNub:null,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:375,question:"It is likely that the governor will exact his pound of flesh ",option:{a:"He will probably demand a hefty  bribe ",b:"He will probably engineer the assassination of his opponents ",c:"He will probably impose crushing new taxes",d:"He will probably demand for and get all that is due to him "},section:"select the option that bost explains the information conveyed in the sentence.",image:"",answer:"d",solution:"",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2008",questionNub:null,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:376,question:"It was too cold for him to go out ",option:{a:"He had a bad cold, and did not go out,",b:"Although it was very cold, he still went out ",c:"As it was very cold, he did not go out",d:"He was afraid to go out that day."},section:"select the option that bost explains the information conveyed in the sentence.",image:"",answer:"c",solution:"",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2008",questionNub:null,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:377,question:"Ado and Abu are always together these days. They must be up to something.",option:{a:"They must have reconciled after their quarrel",b:"They are probably planning something bar",c:"They are capable of a praiseworthy achievement ",d:"They bear some responsibility for what has happened."},section:"select the option that bost explains the information conveyed in the sentence.",image:"",answer:"b",solution:"",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2008",questionNub:null,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:378,question:"He wants the meeting to be adjourned,",option:{a:"He wants the meeting closed ",b:"He wants the meeting cancelled ",c:"He wants the meeting to continue till another day ",d:"He want  the meeting to another day without delay "},section:"select the option that bost explains the information conveyed in the sentence.",image:"",answer:"d",solution:"",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2008",questionNub:null,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:379,question:"My father is one of the vociferous few challenging the company’s appointment of the manager.",option:{a:"My father is the one who shouts with a loud voice against the appointment of the manager",b:"My father and others speak on behalf of the company against the appointment of the manager",c:"My father is one of those objecting to the appointment of the manager",d:"My father is agitated by the appointment of the manager"},section:"select the option that bost explains the information conveyed in the sentence.",image:"",answer:"c",solution:"",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2008",questionNub:null,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:380,question:"The voyagers fetched up in Nigeria",option:{a:"the foreigners finally settled in Nigeria",b:"The journey by sea ended in Nigeria",c:"The travellers made a stopover in Nigeria",d:"The discoverers landed in Nigeria after a long journey,"},section:"select the option that bost explains the information conveyed in the sentence.",image:"",answer:"d",solution:"",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2008",questionNub:null,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:381,question:"In those days in this school, everyone who spoke in a",option:{a:"language other than English paid a fine of ten naira",b:"  Everyone of us paid a fine of ten naira because we did not always speak in English  ",c:" Everyone would pay a fine of ten naira for wanting to use a language other than English ",d:"Those who spoke a language other than English on the premises paid a fine  of ten naira "},section:"select the option that bost explains the information conveyed in the sentence.",image:"",answer:"c",solution:"",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2008",questionNub:null,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:382,question:"The officer has discussed the vexed issue of incessant power failure",option:{a:"In anger, the officer explained the problem of constant power failure",b:"The officer added his voice to the much discussed problem of power cut",c:"The officer's explanations angered those who have suffered the effects of frequency power failure ",d:"The officer told the people not , to be angered by the frequent power cut"},section:"select the option that bost explains the information conveyed in the sentence.",image:"",answer:"b",solution:"",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2008",questionNub:null,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:383,question:"The weather condition now <i>prevailin</i>g in the town is unbearable   ",option:{a:"widespread   ",b:"dominant",c:"unconscious ",d:"disappointed"},section:"choose the option opposite in meaning to the word or phrase in italics.",image:"",answer:"c",solution:"",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2008",questionNub:null,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:384,question:"The lady was  completely <i>nonplussed when her suitor</i>  rejected her gifts ",option:{a:"unpuzzled ",b:"surprised ",c:" unconscious ",d:"disappointed  "},section:"choose the option opposite in meaning to the word or phrase in italics.",image:"",answer:"a",solution:"",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2008",questionNub:null,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:385,question:"As a public officer, he should act with <i>scrupulous</i>  honesty at all times  ",option:{a:"impeccable  ",b:"careless ",c:"transparent ",d:"uncompromising "},section:"choose the option opposite in meaning to the word or phrase in italics.",image:"",answer:"b",solution:"",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2008",questionNub:null,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:386,question:"Men from the agency went into the market in search of <i>unwholesome</i>  food items ",option:{a:"banned ",b:"imported ",c:"healthy ",d:"uncooked "},section:"choose the option opposite in meaning to the word or phrase in italics.",image:"",answer:"b",solution:"",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2008",questionNub:null,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:387,question:"The condition of the hostels has become <i>deplorable </i>",option:{a:"admirable ",b:"regrettable ",c:"bearable ",d:"malignant"},section:"choose the option opposite in meaning to the word or phrase in italics.",image:"",answer:"a",solution:"",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2008",questionNub:null,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:388,question:"The plan to merge the two local government areas has met with much <i>apathy.</i>",option:{a:"hospitality ",b:"criticism ",c:"consideration ",d:"enthusiasm "},section:"choose the option opposite in meaning to the word or phrase in italics.",image:"",answer:"d",solution:"",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2008",questionNub:null,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:389,question:"There is now a <i>dearth</i>  of talent in the industry; she said ",option:{a:"a lack ",b:"an abundance ",c:"a rebirth ",d:"a shortage "},section:"choose the option opposite in meaning to the word or phrase in italics.",image:"",answer:"b",solution:"",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2008",questionNub:null,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:390,question:"The students  <i>vandalized </i> their hostel curing the riot.",option:{a:"  deserted ",b:"Unrepaired  ",c:" protected",d:"decorated."},section:"choose the option opposite in meaning to the word or phrase in italics.",image:"",answer:"b",solution:"",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2008",questionNub:null,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:391,question:"His <i>kind-hearted</i> master bought him a motorcycle",option:{a:" stingy   ",b:"generous    ",c:" shrewd ",d:"angry."},section:"choose the option opposite in meaning to the word or phrase in italics.",image:"",answer:"d",solution:"",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2008",questionNub:null,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:392,question:"<i>Mutual</i> love is what Kabi and Musa have in common, and nothing else.   ",option:{a:" insincere     ",b:"unhappy",c:"one-sided    ",d:"disrespectful. "},section:"choose the option opposite in meaning to the word or phrase in italics.",image:"",answer:"c",solution:"",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2008",questionNub:null,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:393,question:"Always strive to get what is <i>legitimate,</i>",option:{a:"illicit    ",b:"legal",c:" good    ",d:"impure"},section:"choose the option opposite in meaning to the word or phrase in italics.",image:"",answer:"a",solution:"",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2008",questionNub:null,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:394,question:"Some aspects of their culture are <i>out of date</i>",option:{a:"genuine  ",b:"pragmatic ",c:"fashionable ",d:"fake"},section:"choose the option opposite in meaning to the word or phrase in italics.",image:"",answer:"c",solution:"",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2008",questionNub:null,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:395,question:"On the first day of her examination, Amina felt very <i>confident.</i>",option:{a:"excited ",b:"dull  ",c:"beefed up",d:"strung up. "},section:"choose the option opposite in meaning to the word or phrase in italics.",image:"",answer:"b",solution:"",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2008",questionNub:null,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:396,question:"My father is always very <i>frank</i> about his intentions",option:{a:"open   ",b:"objective",c:"secretive",d:"deceitful"},section:"choose the option opposite in meaning to the word or phrase in italics.",image:"",answer:"d",solution:"",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2008",questionNub:null,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:397,question:"The speaker was rather <i>bold</i> in his presentation of the case ",option:{a:"unfair ",b:"reserved ",c:"ashamed ",d:"formal"},section:"choose the option opposite in meaning to the word or phrase in italics.",image:"",answer:"b",solution:"",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2008",questionNub:null,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:398,question:"The doctor tried to <i>soothe</i> the patient before the operation  ",option:{a:"examine   ",b:" treat ",c:" calm ",d:"induce"},section:"choose the option nearest in meaning to the word or phrase In Italics",image:"",answer:"c",solution:"",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2008",questionNub:null,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:399,question:"The charge brought against my brother was hardly <i>tenable\\</i>",option:{a:"sensible  ",b:"defensible   ",c:"meaningful",d:" flimsy"},section:"choose the option nearest in meaning to the word or phrase In Italics",image:"",answer:"a",solution:"",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2008",questionNub:null,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:400,question:"The man described his son as a <i>willful</i> character",option:{a:"   wicked ",b:"obstinate",c:"wild    ",d:"tricky."},section:"choose the option nearest in meaning to the word or phrase In Italics",image:"",answer:"b",solution:"",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2008",questionNub:null,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:401,question:"Our teacher described Agbo's story as a <i>phantom</i>",option:{a:"scary  ",b:"realistic ",c:"fanciful   ",d:"interesting "},section:"choose the option nearest in meaning to the word or phrase In Italics",image:"",answer:"c",solution:"",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2008",questionNub:null,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:402,question:"I find the way she approaches her customers quite <i>repugnant</i> ",option:{a:"unpleasant   ",b:"attractive. ",c:"ungodly    ",d:"encouraging"},section:"choose the option nearest in meaning to the word or phrase In Italics",image:"",answer:"c",solution:"",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2008",questionNub:null,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:403,question:"Participation in the programme is <i>optional</i>",option:{a:"unnecessary   ",b:" recommended",c:"hard to justify   ",d:"a matter of choice"},section:"choose the option nearest in meaning to the word or phrase In Italics",image:"",answer:"d",solution:"",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2008",questionNub:null,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:404,question:"Scientists have <i>invented</i> ways of preserving fruits much longer   ",option:{a:"coined ",b:"devised   ",c:"arranged",d:"organized"},section:"choose the option nearest in meaning to the word or phrase In Italics",image:"",answer:"b",solution:"",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2008",questionNub:null,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:405,question:"The attempt to count the population was <i>largely</i> successful.  ",option:{a:" mostly ",b:"completely   ",c:" hardly",d:"totally."},section:"choose the option nearest in meaning to the word or phrase In Italics",image:"",answer:"a",solution:"",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2008",questionNub:null,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:406,question:"The governor has <i>approved</i>  the award of the contract",option:{a:"appreciated ",b:" acknowledged ",c:"vetoed ",d:"endorsed"},section:"choose the option nearest in meaning to the word or phrase In Italics",image:"",answer:"d",solution:"",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2008",questionNub:null,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:407,question:"I cannot stand Simon, I find his attitude <i>offensive</i>",option:{a:"unapproachable   ",b:" obnoxious ",c:"wicked",d:"  unpardonable"},section:"choose the option nearest in meaning to the word or phrase In Italics",image:"",answer:"b",solution:"",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2008",questionNub:null,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:408,question:"The  man would not <i>withdraw</i>  what hi hid ",option:{a:"take back   ",b:" takeout   ",c:"take",d:"tike from"},section:"choose the option nearest in meaning to the word or phrase In Italics",image:"",answer:"a",solution:"",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2008",questionNub:null,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:409,question:"The <i>disagreement</i> between the two men became obvious during the meeting",option:{a:"insult",b:"confrontation",c:"passion",d:"insinuation"},section:"choose the option nearest in meaning to the word or phrase In Italics",image:"",answer:"b",solution:"",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2008",questionNub:null,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:410,question:"The principal  detested his <i>recalcitrant</i> attitude ",option:{a:"disobedient ",b:"arrogant ",c:"voracious ",d:"vengeful "},section:"choose the option nearest in meaning to the word or phrase In Italics",image:"",answer:"a",solution:"",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2008",questionNub:null,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:411,question:"The union officials suddenly became <i>reactive</i>",option:{a:"unruly ",b:"impatient ",c:"calm  ",d:"submissive "},section:"choose the option nearest in meaning to the word or phrase In Italics",image:"",answer:"a",solution:"",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2008",questionNub:null,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:412,question:"The popularity of the military dictator <i>waned</i>  after war ",option:{a:"increased ",b:"changed ",c:"declined ",d:"skyrocketed."},section:"choose the option nearest in meaning to the word or phrase In Italics",image:"",answer:"c",solution:"",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2008",questionNub:null,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:413,question:"The chairman addressed the………… ",option:{a:"university French teacher",b:"university of French teachers ",c:"French one hundred university teachers ",d:"university French one hundred teacher "},section:"choose the option  best completes the gap(s) .",image:"",answer:"a",solution:"",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2008",questionNub:null,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:414,question:"Kanuri is a language.........",option:{a:"I can't speak it well ",b:"that I cant speak it well ",c:"of which I can't speak it well",d:"I can't speak well "},section:"choose the option  best completes the gap(s) .",image:"",answer:"d",solution:"",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2008",questionNub:null,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:415,question:"Last Tuesday, Ochonu asked me.........",option:{a:" had I come yesterday ",b:"did you come yesterday ",c:"whether I had come the day before ",d:"If I had come yesterday"},section:"choose the option  best completes the gap(s) .",image:"",answer:"c",solution:"",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2008",questionNub:null,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:416,question:"The young man has..... to sober...……  after being drunk.",option:{a:"began/up ",b:"begun/in    ",c:"begun/up    ",d:"began/down"},section:"choose the option  best completes the gap(s) .",image:"",answer:"c",solution:"",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2008",questionNub:null,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:417,question:"My mother had........  the fire wood before it began to rain. ",option:{a:"splitting ",b:"splited  ",c:"splitted",d:"splitting"},section:"choose the option  best completes the gap(s) .",image:"",answer:"a",solution:"",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2008",questionNub:null,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:418,question:"The police officer warned the... communities against taking the law……… hands",option:{a:"feuding/into their own ",b:"feudal/ to their own ",c:"feuding to their own   ",d:"feudal/in their own"},section:"choose the option  best completes the gap(s) .",image:"",answer:"a",solution:"",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2008",questionNub:null,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:419,question:"Agbo could not travel as he had come...…  influenza",option:{a:"over with ",b:"down with ",c:"in from ",d:"on to "},section:"choose the option  best completes the gap(s) .",image:"",answer:"b",solution:"",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2008",questionNub:null,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:420,question:"When he.........from his journey, I want to see him.",option:{a:"returns ",b:"might have returned ",c:"returned ",d:"must have returned "},section:"choose the option  best completes the gap(s) .",image:"",answer:"a",solution:"",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2008",questionNub:null,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:421,question:"I knocked his door, but he.........",option:{a:"has already ten ",b:"left already ",c:"would already leave",d:"had already left "},section:"choose the option  best completes the gap(s) .",image:"",answer:"d",solution:"",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2008",questionNub:null,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:422,question:"………of the students  turned up, so the lecture was cancelled.",option:{a:"few ",b:"Little",c:" A few  ",d:" A little"},section:"choose the option  best completes the gap(s) .",image:"",answer:"a",solution:"",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2008",questionNub:null,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:423,question:"He brought a  ……… against his neighbour.",option:{a:"complaint ",b:"complains",c:"complain ",d:"complaining "},section:"choose the option  best completes the gap(s) .",image:"",answer:"a",solution:"",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2008",questionNub:null,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:424,question:"The hotel lacks the ..……. for accommodating so many guests.",option:{a:"ability",b:"capability",c:"capacity",d:"competence "},section:"choose the option  best completes the gap(s) .",image:"",answer:"c",solution:"",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2008",questionNub:null,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:425,question:"If you are not careful, you would .......... your money.",option:{a:"toss  ",b:"lose",c:"loose   ",d:"lost"},section:"choose the option  best completes the gap(s) .",image:"",answer:"b",solution:"",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2008",questionNub:null,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:426,question:"You must practise in order to................perfection.",option:{a:"obtain   ",b:"have",c:"get ",d:"achieve"},section:"choose the option  best completes the gap(s) .",image:"",answer:"d",solution:"",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2008",questionNub:null,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:427,question:"The condition of the room was so………... so I went outside ",option:{a:"intolerant",b:"intolerable ",c:"inconstant ",d:"invariabl "},section:"choose the option  best completes the gap(s) .",image:"",answer:"b",solution:"",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2008",questionNub:null,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:428,question:"You don't like Mathematics, ........... you?",option:{a:"do",b:"don't",c:"cant ",d:"can "},section:"choose the option  best completes the gap(s) .",image:"",answer:"a",solution:"",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2008",questionNub:null,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:429,question:"They have had their debt written ........... by their creditors.",option:{a:"down ",b:"on ",c:"up ",d:"off"},section:"choose the option  best completes the gap(s) .",image:"",answer:"d",solution:"",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2008",questionNub:null,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:430,question:"Uncle Ochai now has enough money to complete his…….. building.",option:{a:"two storey ",b:"two-storeyed ",c:"two-story ",d:"two storeyed "},section:"choose the option  best completes the gap(s) .",image:"",answer:"a",solution:"",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2008",questionNub:null,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:431,question:"By the end of this month……….for three years in this school.",option:{a:"I will study ",b:"I  will have been studying ",c:"I  am studying",d:"I had been studying "},section:"choose the option  best completes the gap(s) .",image:"",answer:"b",solution:"",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2008",questionNub:null,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:432,question:"He ……… the picture on table",option:{a:"laid ",b:"lay ",c:" lied  ",d:"Iain "},section:"choose the option  best completes the gap(s) .",image:"",answer:"a",solution:"",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2008",questionNub:null,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:433,question:"Sc<u>oo</u> led ",option:{a:"cold ",b:"could ",c:"court",d:"you"},section:"choose the option that has the same vowel sound as the represented by the letter(s) underlined.",image:"",answer:"d",solution:"",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2008",questionNub:null,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:434,question:"sh<u>ir</u> t  ",option:{a:"shut ",b:"shade",c:"surf",d:"shed"},section:"choose the option that has the same vowel sound as the represented by the letter(s) underlined.",image:"",answer:"c",solution:"",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2008",questionNub:null,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:435,question:"w<u>ai</u> st ",option:{a:"fete ",b:"says",c:"plait",d:"breakfast "},section:"choose the option that has the same vowel sound as the represented by the letter(s) underlined.",image:"",answer:"d",solution:"",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2008",questionNub:null,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:436,question:"<u>th</u> atch ",option:{a:"clothing   ",b:"mother",c:"then ",d:"method"},section:"choose the option that has the same consonant sound as the one represented by the letter(s) underlined.",image:"",answer:"d",solution:"",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2008",questionNub:null,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:437,question:"<u> ch</u> ateau  ",option:{a:"chart    ",b:"church ",c:"champagne",d:" chemical."},section:"choose the option that has the same consonant sound as the one represented by the letter(s) underlined.",image:"",answer:"c",solution:"",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2008",questionNub:null,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:438,question:" ju<u>dge</u> ",option:{a:"measure",b:"General ",c:"Pressure",d:"Grace "},section:"choose the option that has the same consonant sound as the one represented by the letter(s) underlined.",image:"",answer:"b",solution:"",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2008",questionNub:null,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:439,question:"",option:{a:"distress",b:"control",c:"bottom",d:"report"},section:"choose the option has a different stress pattern from the others.",image:"",answer:"c",solution:"",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2008",questionNub:null,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:440,question:"",option:{a:"original",b:"deplorable",c:"ability",d:"revolution"},section:"choose the option has a different stress pattern from the others.",image:"",answer:"d",solution:"",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2008",questionNub:null,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:441,question:"",option:{a:"release",b:"exit",c:"exchange",d:"explode"},section:"choose the option has a different stress pattern from the others.",image:"",answer:"b",solution:"",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2008",questionNub:null,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:442,question:"",option:{a:"bachelor",b:"forget",c:"cement",d:"ago"},section:"choose the option that has the stress on the first syllable.",image:"",answer:"a",solution:"",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2008",questionNub:null,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:443,question:"",option:{a:"librarian",b:"immunize",c:"militia",d:"continuous"},section:"choose the option that has the stress on the first syllable.",image:"",answer:"a",solution:"",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2008",questionNub:null,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:444,question:"",option:{a:"july",b:"litereture",c:"august",d:"oesophagus"},section:"choose the option that has the stress on the first syllable.",image:"",answer:"d",solution:"",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2008",questionNub:null,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:445,question:"xenophobia   ",option:{a:"XEndphobia   ",b:"xeNOphobia",c:" xenoPHObia     ",d:"xenophoBIA."},section:"choose the appropriate  stress pattern from the options. The syllables are written in capital letters.",image:"",answer:"c",solution:"",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2008",questionNub:null,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:446,question:"photography ",option:{a:"phoTOgraphy   ",b:"PHOtograhy",c:" photoGRAphy   ",d:"photograPHY"},section:"choose the appropriate  stress pattern from the options. The syllables are written in capital letters.",image:"",answer:"a",solution:"",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2008",questionNub:null,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:447,question:"melodramatic ",option:{a:"MEIodramatic  ",b:"meLOdramatic",c:" meloDRAmatic ",d:"melodraMAtic."},section:"choose the appropriate  stress pattern from the options. The syllables are written in capital letters.",image:"",answer:"d",solution:"",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2008",questionNub:null,hasPassage:0,category:"others"}],s={subject:e,status:200,total:75,data:t};export{t as data,s as default,o as status,e as subject,a as total};
